Damián Oscar Amigo





dam.oscar.amigo@gmail.com



Erlangen, Germany



MY GOALS

I am passionate about programming, constantly training myself. Right now I'm down the road of data analysis with Python. I am looking for a company where I can put myself to the test and continue to increase my knowledge towards my goal of Data Science and AI.

MY STRENGTHS

Excellent organization, skills and abilities to translate the business vision into an effective high-level architecture and strategy. A leader with collaborative skills to create important relationships, required to deliver excellent solutions. Strong analytical and problem solving skills, lateral thinking, extensive knowledge in many languages (C#, Java, PHP, MySQL, PostgreSQL) with specialization in Python.

LANGUAGES

EDUCATION

Spanish: Native

German: A2

English: B1

2000 - 2004 Informatics Engineering University of Lincoln, Bs. As. Argentina

2015 Certification Xámarin: Imparted by Microsoft

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Nov. 2021 - Nov.2022 CDMX, México

UNIFIN FINANCIERA

Developer

- API development, management and deployment.
- Python, Django REST Framework, Celery, JWT, Mysql, PostgreSQL.
- Microsoft Teams, GitLab, GitBucket, Yira, Postman, PgAdmin.
- Agile methodologies SCRUM, Git.
- AWS, GCP, Docker.
- Training for new programmers, code refactoring.
- Debug and identification of errors in real time.
- Monitoring and resolution of incidents..

Nov. 2017 - jul. 2021 Buenos Aires, Argentina

WORKANA

Web Developer

- Cloud services (AWS).
- Python (Django), HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL.
- Excellent debugging skills..
- Program development life cycle.
- Management of web platforms, WP, Prestashop..
- Development of Landing pages, websites and eCommerce.

Nov. 2011 – jul. 2017 CDMX, México

SPERTA IMAGI

Developer

- Development in C#, PHP, HTML, CSS, JS, Mysql, Python and Java.
- Strong problem solving and reverse engineering.
- Frontend/backend experience in web development.
- Agile methodologies SCRUM, GitHub, Jira.
- Development of APPs for Android.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- As a personal project and hobby, I have created a microscopy image analysis program, which analyzes different protein expression surface on different biological tissues and returns the user a data sheet with the different proteins contained in the images.
- Another ongoing personal project I'm working on is an automated cryptocurrency trading system. This system works with a history of data that is used to make the decision whether it is a good time to sell or buy said crypto asset using thirdparty APIs. I am studying everything related to AWS to take advantage of these tools and set up my system there.